Narrator: Stressed Sally
A: wake up at 7 o’clock
Narrator: 2
A: take a shower
Narrator: 3
A: get dressed
Narrator: 4
A: put on make-up
Narrator: 5
A: have a coffee
Narrator: 6
A: go to work by bus
Narrator: 7
A: get to work
Narrator: 8
A: start work at 8:30
Narrator: 9
A: have lunch at work
Narrator: 10
A: finish work at 6:30
Narrator: 11
A: go shopping
Narrator: 12
A: get home late
Narrator: 13
A: do the housework
Narrator: 14
A: have pizza for dinner
Narrator: 15
A: check emails
Narrator: 16
A: go to bed
Narrator: Relaxed Robbie
B: get up at 8 o’clock
Narrator: 18
B: shave
Narrator: 19
B: take the dog for a walk
Narrator: 20
B: have breakfast
Narrator: 21
B: walk to work
Narrator: 22
B: go home early
Narrator: 23
B: go to Italian classes
Narrator: 24
B: see friends
Narrator: 25
B: make dinner
Narrator: 26
B: relax
Narrator: 27
B: take a bath
Narrator: 28
B: sleep for eight hours